Step 1: click (960, 550) [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center of the screen. The search box is located below the Google
Step 2: click (960, 549) [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showing trending searches below t
Step 3: click (960, 549) [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showing trending searches below t
Step 4: click (885, 550) [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showing trending searches below t
Step 5: find_and_click (1215, 577) [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showing trending searches below t
Step 6: type  [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with the search box visible in the center. The search box appears to be active (there's a
Step 7: type  [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. Looking at the task history, I've already typed 'ScreenPi
Step 8: key  [OK]\NI can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. Looking at the task history, I've already typed 'ScreenPi
Step 9: key  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showin
Step 10: key  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There is a dropdown menu showi
Step 11: click (960, 549) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showin
Step 12: click (960, 550) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Google homepage with a search box in the center. There's a dropdown menu showin